

CONTACT

0906-706-6040
ganilynavonalcontin@gmail.com
San Jose Road, Zone 2,
Zamboanga City, Philippines
November 18, 2002
Filipino

Socials

Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/avy.alc ontin?mibextid=LQQJ4d

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/vonna

min/

Github: Avon Alcontin

SKILLS

Language:

English

Filipino

Language:

English

Filipino

GANILYN AVON B. ALCONTIN

UX DESIGNER/QA DESIGNER

I am Ganilyn Avon Alcontin, an incoming fourth-year student studying Bachelor of Science in Computer Science at Western Mindanao State University. As a UX Designer and QA Engineer, I am passionate about creating intuitive user experiences and ensuring the highest quality standards for software. I excel in bridging the gap between design and functionality, utilizing my skills to deliver visually appealing and user-friendly products. With a meticulous eye for detail and a strong commitment to continuous learning, I am dedicated to making a positive impact in the ever-evolving world of technology.

EDUCATION

Secondary

August 2018 - March 2020 **Senior High School**

Zamboanga City HIgh School Main- Intergrated Senior High School

Computer System Servicing NC II With Honor

Junior High School

June 2014 - March 2018 Zamboanga City HIgh School Main

Primary

June 2008 - March 2014
Zamboanga East and West Elementary Central School
With Honor

INTEREST

- Technology Design
- Freelance

AFFILIATION

Technology staff of Aura Flower Shop (2017-present)

CERTIFICATION

• Computer System Servicing

NC II Holder

(2019)

EXPERIENCE

2022-2023

APARTMENT RENTAL MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

Quality Assurance Engineer SOFTWARE ENGINEERING 1 & 2

2023- PRESENT

AI-Driven Syllabus Generation using OpenAI Language Model for Improving Course Design

RESEARCHER

• THESIS 1 & 2